Charles Isaac Hansen 431 N 1300 W Salt Lake City, Utah 84116 (801) 649-7912 chans7692@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Since I started working I have gained lots of experience in a number of different fields. I have worked in construction, maintenance, manufacturing, sales, web programming, merchandising, and transportation.

I am a hard working and dedicated worker who is always trying to improve myself. I hope to have the chance to show you what I am capable of.

WORK EXPERIENCE

>	Night Watchman / Maintenance	Beck's Sanitation (2018 – 2019)		
>	Delivery Driver	Auto Zone (2018)		
>	Delivery Driver	Dealer Staffing (Larry H. Miller Dealerships) (2016 – 2017)		
>	Merchandiser / Sales Clerk	Shoppers Boot Corral (2015 – 2016)		
>	Assembly Tech	Desert Tech (2014)		
>	Merchandiser	Sam's Club (Salt Lake City Branch) (2013 – 2014)		
>	WordPress Web Developer	BlueRuby Media (2013)		
>	Tank Farm Operator	Washakie Renewable Energy / CCP Enterprises / United Fuel		
		Supply (2013)		
>	Platform Maintenance Tech	UTA (Utah Transit Authority) (2012 - 2013)		
>	Warehouse Maintenance Tech	Standard Restaurant Supply / Bountiful Baby "A division of D.P. Creations" (2011 - 2012)		
\triangleright	Trainee/General Laborer	O'Brien Property Maintenance (2007 - 2010)		

SKILLS

	HTML5		CSS3
>	JavaScript	>	NodeJs
>	React	>	Axios
>	Express	>	MongoDB

EDUCATION

Attended V School coding boot-camp in downtown Salt Lake City Utah from March 2019 - June2019